Guide to the Le Bayou Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Subscriptions, 1934-1963
  - Bookstores, Libraries, Organizations, and Universities, 1937-1963
    - Creighton University; Nebraska, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 211)
    - Daniel Baker College; Texas; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 212)
    - Dartmouth College; New Hampshire, 1951-1955 (Box 8, Folder 213)
    - Decatur Public Library; Illinois; gift subscription, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 214)
    - Denver Public Library; Colorado, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 215)
    - Dunbarton College; Washington D.C., 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - East Texas State Teacher’s College, 1938, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - Ecole Superiéure de Perfectionement et d’Entraînement des Professeurs Français à l’etranger, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 218)
    - Emmanuel College Library; Massachusetts, 1951-1955, 1944-1946 (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - Fall River Public Library; Massachusetts; gift subscription, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 220)
    - Florida State College for Women; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 221)
    - Free Public Library; New Jersey; gift subscription, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 222)
    - French and European Publications, 1951, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 223)
    - Georgetown University; Washington D.C.; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 224)
    - Goosecreek Independent School District; Houston, Texas, 1951-1953, 1955, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 225)
    - Grant Technical College, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 226)
    - Gulf-Park College; Mississippi, 1947-1957 (Box 8, Folder 227)
    - Gustavus Adolphus College; Minnesota, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 228)
    - Harding High School; Oklahoma, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 229)
    - Harvard College Library, 1947-1961 (Box 8, Folder 230)
    - Hope College; Michigan, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 231)
    - Houston Public Library, 1936-1962 (Box 8, Folder 232)
    - Howard University; Washington D.C., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 233)
    - Idaho State College Library, 1950-1951, 1955, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 234)
    - Immaculata College; Pennsylvania, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 235)
    - Indiana University Library, 1947, 1952, 1955, 1959-1963 (Box 8, Folder 236)
    - Institut d’Anglais Faculté des Lettres; France, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 237)
    - Institut Français de Washington; membership card, undated (Box 8, Folder 238)
    - Ithaca Public Schools; New York, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 239)
    - Kentucky Wesleyan College, 1943, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 240)
    - Lake Arthur High School; Louisiana; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 241)
    - Lakehead College; Port Arthur, Canada, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 242)
    - Lawrenceville School Library; New Jersey; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 243)
    - Lee Junior College; Texas, 1948-1954 (Box 8, Folder 244)
    - Librairie Française; Mexique, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 245)
    - Librairie de France; New York, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 246)
    - Librarie Gallimard; Paris, France, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Libraries Julie Billiart; Massachusetts, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Librarie la Proue; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Librairie Larousse; Paris, France, 1952, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Libraireie Bon Plaisir; Paris, France, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Librairie Lipton; New York, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Library of Congress; Periodical Division, 1937-1950 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Louisiana State Library, 1946-1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Louisiana State University, 1946-1961 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Lynwood Unified School District Library; California, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Maine State Library, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - McNeese State College; Louisiana, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Miami University; Ohio, 1952-1962 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Michigan State College Library, 1956-1958 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Middlebury College; Vermont, 1943-1949 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Midwestern University; Texas, 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Mills College, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Milton Public Library; Massachusetts; gift subscription, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Mississippi State College; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Museum Publications; New York, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - National Institute of Professional Services, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - New York Public Library, 1937, 1948-1954, 1956-1962 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - New York State Library, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Niagara Falls Public Library, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - North Texas State College Library, 1951-1956, 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Northeast Louisiana State College, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Northeastern Oklahoma A&M College, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Northwestern University Library; Illinois, 1943-1946, 1948-1958, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - N.W. Ayer and Sons; Directory of Newspapers and Periodicals; Pennsylvania, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Office Français d’Information Culturelles; Paris, France, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Ohio State University Library, 1952-1959 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Ohio Wesleyan University, 1958-1962 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Oklahoma State University, 1955-1962 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Ottawa University; Kansas, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Phillips Exeter Academy; New Hampshire, 1954-1954 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Phnom Penh USIS Library, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Pennsylvania State University Library, 1943-1962 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Plantation Book Shop; New Orleans, Louisiana, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Prairie View University; Texas, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Princeton University; New Jersey, 1947, 1950-1954, 1958-1959, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Queen Mary College; London, England, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - The Reading Institute; Boston, Massachusetts, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Rhode Island State College, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Rice University; The Fondren Library, 1948-1949, 1953-1954, 1956-1959 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Ricour and Chevillet; Paris, France, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Rochester Public Library; New York; gift subscription, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Rutgers University; New Jersey, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Sam Houston State Teacher’s College; Estill Library, 1947, 1956-1963 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Scripps College Library; California, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Secrétariat Province de Québec, Canada, 1950, 1953-1954, 1956, 1958, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Smith College; Massachusetts; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Societé des Écrivains; Ile Maurice, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Societé Françaises de New York, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Societé d’Histoire du Théâtre; Paris, France, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Societé Historique du Nouvel-Ontario; Canada, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Societé des Professeurs Français; New York, 1947-1951 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Societé Shell d’Indochine, 1948-1951 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Southern Louisiana Institute, 1944-1947, 1951, 1953, 1955, 1958-1960, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Southern Methodist University, 1947, 1951-1953, 1955, 1957-1959, 1960, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Southern State College; Arkansas, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - St. Bonaventure University; New York, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - St. Joseph’s Prepatory Seminary, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - St. Louis Public Library, 1956-1962 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - St. Louis University; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - St. Vincent’s College; Louisiana, 1948-1950 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Stanford University Library, 1941, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - State University of Iowa, 1947, 1954-1956, 1958, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Stephens College; gift subscription, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Syndicat des Journalistes et Écrivains; Paris, France, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Texas State College for Women, 1947, 192-1953, 1955-1956, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Texas Southern University; Houston, Texas, 1952-1953, 1955-1963 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Texas State University for Negroes, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Texas Technological College, 1953-1962 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Toronto Public Library, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Trinity College Library; Washington D.C., 1950-1957, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Trinity University; San Antonio, Texas, 1957, 1959, 1960-1963 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Tulane University; Howard Tilton Memorial Library; Louisiana, 1941-1946, 1948-1955, 1957-1963 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Université Laval; Québec, Canada, 1942-1961 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Universities and Organizations; list, undated (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - United States Military Academy Library; West Point, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - University of Alabama, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - University of Arizona, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - University of Arkansas, 1947, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - University of British Columbia; Canada, 1947, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - University of Buffalo; New York, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - University of California, 1952-1956 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - University of Chattanooga; Tennessee, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - University of Chicago, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - University of Colorado Libraries, 1947-1953 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - University of Denver Libraries, 1948, 1951-1957 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - University of Detroit, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - University of Georgia, 1947-1948, 1950-1952, 1954-1957, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - University of Houston International Student Center, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - University of Houston Library, 1955-1963 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - University of Houston Library; Contracts, 1950-1954 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - University of Houston Library; Correspondence, 1948-1955 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - University of Houston Library; Debit Notes; (service d’Echange), 1951-1955 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - University of Houston Library; to Le Bayou, service d’Echange, 1950-1954 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - University of Houston Library; Receipts; service d’Echange, 1950-1962 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - The University of Houston Press, 1950-1955 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - University of Iowa, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - University of Illinois Library, 1947-1963 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - University of Kansas, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - University of Kentucky, 1948-1961 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - University of London Library, 1961-1963 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - University of Maine Library, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - University of Manitoba Library, 1959-1962 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - University of Miami; Florida, 1951, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - University of Michigan, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - University of Mississippi, 1953-1962 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Université de Montréal, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - University of North Carolina, 1950-1955, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - University of Notre Dame; Indiana, 1941, 1957-1963 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - University of Oregon, 1947, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1953-1956, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - University of the South, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - University of South Carolina Library, 1941-1944 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - University of Southern California, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - University of Southern Louisiana, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - University of St. Thomas Library, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - University of Tennessee, 1949-1954, 1956, 1958, 1960, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - University of Texas Library, 1940-1961 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - University of Texas College of Dentistry, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - University of Toronto Library, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - University of Virginia, 1954-1959 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - University of Washington Library, 1942, 1948-1962 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - University of Wisconsin Library, 1941-1948, 1951-1955, 1958-1963 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Ursuline Academy; New York; Texas, 1941-1947, 1949-1953, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - USIS Library; American Consulate; Martinique, 1957-1960 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Walla Walla College, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Wantagh School Library, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Washington University Library; Missouri, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Wayne University; Michigan, 1947-1961 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Wesleyan College; Georgia, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Western Michigan College of Education, 1942-1943, 1945-1946, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Western Reserve University; Ohio, 1948-1949, 1957-1960, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - West Virginia University, 1941, 1950-1956, 1958-1962 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Yale University Library; Connecticut, 1941-1951, 1955, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - Service d’Echange, 1937-1963
    This subseries consists of 170 folders of materials that relate to the exchange of Le Bayou with other publications, such as the Berkeley Review and France-Amerique. It is organized alphabetically, and then by date.
    - L’Acropole; Paris France, 1949-1952 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - L’Action Universaire; Montreal, Canada, 1951-1954 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - L’Age Nouveau; Paris, France, 1947-1950, 1957, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - American Consul for Nationalities Service; New York, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Les Annales; Paris, France, 1951, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Anthologie Poètique Contemporaine; Corsica, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - L’Arche; Paris, France, 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - L’Architecture d’Aujord ‘hui; Boulogne, Italie, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - L’Argus de la Presse; Paris, France, 1958, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - The Berkeley Review; California, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - La Boite a Clous; Bordeaux, France, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Le Bonhomme Froissart; Valenciennes, France, 1950-1952 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - La Bouteille a la Mer; Paris, France, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Les Cahiers d’Études Cathares; Carcassonne, France, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Les Cahiers des Jeunes Écrivains Belges; Bruxelles, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Les Cahiers du Peuple; Paris, France, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Cahiers du Sud; Marseilles, France, 1946, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Les Cahiers du Symbolisme Chrétien; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Les Cahiers Jean Tousseul; Ath, Belgique, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - The Canadian Modern Language Review; Toronto, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Le Carabin; Université Laval; Québec, Canada, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Les Carnets Poètiques Nord-Africains; Algérie, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Le Cocotier; Liége, Belgique, 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Comptes Rendus de Athénée; Louisiana, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Il Corriere di Poggia; Italie, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Le Courrier de la Presse; Paris, France, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Le Courrier des Lettres; Paris, France, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Le Courrier Littéraire d’Outre-Mer; Algérie, 1951-1954 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Demande de Numero; Echantillon, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Le Digeste Français; Montréal, Canada, 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Les Documents Européennes S.A.; Paris, France, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Echanges avec Autres Publications, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Ecrits de Paris; Paris, France, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Les Editions de l’Arbe; Montréal, France, 1943, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Éditions Seghers; Paris, France, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Les Éditions Variétes; Canada, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - L’Education Nationale; Paris, France, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Les Elites Françaises; Paris, France, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Elites Françaises, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Empreintes; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1947-1951 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Epitres; Paris, France, 1947, 1952-1953, 1955, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - L’Espirit Créateur; Minnesota, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - L’Essor; Ile Maurice, 1947, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Les Etoiles; Paris, France, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Etudes; Paris, France, 1948, 1953, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Les Etudes Américaines; Paris, France, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Les Etudes Classiques, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Fabula; Argentina, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Fiction; Paris, France, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - La Floride Française, 1955, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Fontaine; Paris, France, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - France-Amerique; New York, 1944-1954, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - France Amerique; Paris, France, 1937-1938, 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - France-Asie; Saïgon, 1946, 1948-1952, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - France-Poésie; Paris, France, 1948-1950 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - The French American Review; Washington D.C., 1948 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - The French Review; New York, 1940, 1949-1950, 1955, 1958, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - La Gazette des Lettres; Paris, France, 1946-1952 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Grove Press; New York, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Hebdo-Monde; Paris, France, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Hémisphères; New York, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - L’Heure Française; New York, 1946-1954 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Horizon; Nantes, France, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Igazsag; Romania, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - L’Illustration; Paris, France, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Impressions; Paris, France, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Institut Français d’Amerique Latine; Mexico, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Institut Français d’Haiti, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Institut des Hautes Etudes Americaines; Paris, France, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Instituto de Cultura Hispanica; Madrid, Spain, 1951-1952, 1954, 1958, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Institut Pedagogique National; Paris, France, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Le Jeune Faune; Belgique, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Jeunes Lettres Hennuyeres, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Le Journal d’Egypte; Alexandrie, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Le Journal des Poètes; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1948-1951 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Littérature Moderne; Milan, Italie, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Les Lettres Françaises; Paris, France, 1943, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Lettres et Poésie; Paris, France, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Lettres du Monde; Paris, France, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Lettres Nouvelles; Liége, Belgique, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Libertê 58; Montréal, Canada, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - The Literary Review; New Jersey, 1957, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Lit Tout; Paris, France, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Lu et Vu; Washington D.C., 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - L’Unique; Orléans, France, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Ma Boheme; France, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Maintenant; Paris, France, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Marginales; France, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Meanjin; Australia, 1950-1952 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - The Mediterranean and Eurafrica; New York, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Le Menure; Paris, France, 1949-1953 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Mercure de France; Paris, France, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Monde Nouveau-Paru; Paris, France, 1952-1953, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Mondes d’Orient; Paris, France, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - La Nef; Algérie, 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Les Nouvelles Littéraires; Paris, France, 1950, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - La Nouvell Releve; Montréal, Canada, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Nouvelle Revue de l’Economie Contemporaine; Paris, France, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - La Nouvelle Revue Française; Paris, France, 1954, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - New Mexico Quarterly Review, 1949-1955, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Occidental; New York, 1949-1950 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Oeuvres Nouvelles; Paris, France, 1948-1950 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Ophrys; France, 1947-1949 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - L’Opinion Wallonne; Liège, Belgique, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Pandiffusion; Paris, France, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Paris – Les Arts et Les Lettres; Paris, France, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Le Parthénon; Paris, France, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Paru; Editions Odile Pathé; Paris, France, 1946-1950, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Periodica; Montréal, Canada, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Periples; Maroc, 1948, 1951, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Le Phare; Rhode Island, 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Plaisir de France; Paris, France, 1947-1948, 1954, 1959, 1961, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Points; Paris, France, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Points et Contrepoints; France, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Pourquoi Pas?; Belgique, 1948-1952 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Pour la Victoire; New York, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - La Premier Chance; Belgique, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Preview; California, 1950-1952 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Quadrige; Paris, France, 1946-1948 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Quebec Wallonie; Liège, Belgique, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Le Radeau de la Meduse; Lyon, France, 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Radiodiffusion – Télévision Française; Paris, France, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Le Recueil; Québec, Canada, 1940-1948 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Relations; Montrèal, Canada, 1947, 1953, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Renaissances; Paris, France, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Rencontre; Lausanne, Suisse, 1950-1953 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - Ressegna Mediterranea; Italie, 1949, 1951-1954 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Revista Interamericana; Columbia, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - La Revue de l’Alliance Française; Paris, France, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - La Revue du Bas-Poitou; Bordeaux, France, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - La Revue du Caire; Egypte, 1951-1952, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Revue de Défense Nationale; France, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - La Revue Dominicaine; Montréal, Canada, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Revue de l’Ecole Normale Primaire et de la Section Normale Moyenne de l’Etat; Belgique, 1947-1949, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Revue Guadeloupeene; Antilles Françaises, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - Revue Hommes et Mondes; Paris, France, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Revue Indépendante; Paris, France, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - La Revue des Lettres Modernes; Paris, France, 1954-1955, 1961, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - La Revue Méditerranéenne; Piédmont, 1946-1950 (Box 10, Folder 139)
    - La Revue Moderne; Paris, France, 1950-1953 (Box 10, Folder 140)
    - Revue Moderne des Arts et de la Vie; Paris, France, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 141)
    - La Revue Nationale; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1947-1949 (Box 10, Folder 142)
    - La Revue Neuve; Paris, France, 1948-1952 (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Revue Palladienne; Paris, France, 1949-1953 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - La Revue de Paris; France, 1947-1950, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Revue Partir; Bruxelles, Belgique, 1947-1948, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Revue de la Pensée Française; New York, 1946, 1957-1961 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Roman; France, undated (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Service d’Echange; General Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Service d’Echange; Miscellaneous, 1936, 1942-1944, 1946-1955, 1957-1963 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Service d’Echange; Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1937, 1940, 1948-1952, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Septembre; Nice, France, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 152)
    - Sève; Ile Maurice, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 153)
    - Le Sextent; France, 1950-1953 (Box 10, Folder 154)
    - Signes du Temps; France, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 155)